[menacing music playing]
- [breathing heavily]
- [Robert] I got him.
Now. now. Settle down. boy.
- Shit.
- [Luke] You fucking lied to me.
[Robert] Don't get so worked up.
We did the best we could.
[Luke]
Oh. you did the best we could? Fuck that!
- Stop it. Stop it!
- [Luke] You fuck! I fucking hate you!
- You wanna help-- Don't you fu--
- Max is here.
- What?
- [Crystal] Max is here.
If he finds out that we lost Anna.
I don't know what he's going to do.
[Robert] Come on now.
get a hold of yourself.
[breathes heavily]
- [music ends]
- [knocks]
Hey. where is she?
Well. that's not very friendly. is it?
Aren't you gonna say hello first?
Where's Anna?
Wow.
It's so weird to see you here.
I remember when you used to take walks
along the river
and I would follow you. remember?
You don't have her.
[breathes shakily] She was... [stammers]
They were fighting and then
I couldn't keep her and she ran out.
She jumped in the water.
I was going to look for her.
but they were... they were fighting.
It was just... [stammers]
...a couple of minutes ago.
[gasps]
Don't touch her.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm Luke.
I just want to tell you I...
[breathes shakily] ...I'm sorry.
[Max] Hmm.
I was so mean to you.
You didn't deserve that.
But you were mean too.
[Crystal breathes shakily]
We're even now. right?
We're even.
I forgive you if you forgive me.
- Hmm.
- [hammer cocks]
- [screams]
- No!
[Crystal grunting. groaning]
- [screams]
- [Robert] Luke!
[grunts. groans]
- [Crystal sobs]
- [Robert] Oh. my God.
Oh. shit.
You got shot in the gut.
You need help right away.
but out here. you're fucked.
- Hey. little sister. look at me.
- [Crystal] What?
Hey. look at me. While you die.
don't forget this face.
Don't forget the face of the little boy
you tormented for a long time.
You think it's funny now? [chuckles]
Die.
Hiya. Dad.
Only the devil
would kill his own sister.
If I'm the devil. what are you?
Boy. I'm going to show you.
[grunts]
[grunts. groaning]
[Crystal grunts]
[Crystal sobbing]
[tense music playing]
[screams]
[muffled screaming]
[speaks Spanish]
You know what that means?
No. of course not.
You never bothered to learn.
It means "bad dog."
You're gonna pay for what you do here.
I don't think I will.
[Robert] Don't you do that! Goddamn it!
[groans] Jesus Christ! [groans]
[Max] All right. now if you'll excuse me.
I have to go open a restaurant.
[Robert] Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey. you get back here now.
Now. enough is enough.
You open this goddamn thing up.
you hear me?
Don't you do it. you motherfucker!
Don't you do it!
Enough is enough. here!
Let me out of here!
No. No! No! [screams]
[screaming]
[menacing music playing]
[crate rattling]
[music continues]
[music ends]
[reporter on radio] This is not a test.
Hurricane Wesley
is going to be massive. folks.
It's expected to hit a Category 5
by the time it reaches landfall
with sustained winds over 170...
[passenger]
Will you just fucking use Waze?
- Residents of Georgia and...
- [driver shushes] Holly's asleep.
I'm just saying maybe you shouldn't
have gotten off the highway.
[driver] Well. maybe you shouldn't
have fucked Holly's soccer coach.
[passenger] That was. like. two years ago.
[driver] Yeah.
well. forgiveness takes time. Heidi.
[Heidi] Oh. please.
you're still holding on to that.
- Huh?
- [driver] I'm trying--
- Oh. shit!
- [Heidi screams]
[grunts] Oh. my God. Oh. Oh. my God.
[Holly] What just happened?
- [driver] She ran out!
- [Heidi] Ma'am. are you okay?
- [driver] Okay. Uh...
- [Holly] Uh. Mom?
[breathing shakily]
I'll get you a new one.
Can I get a ride to my car?
[inmates chattering]
[guard] Hey. Bowden. good news.
You just made bail. so you can be
out of here in a couple of hours.
Good timing. Storm's coming.
[announcer] The City of Savannah
Chamber of Commerce welcomes Max Cady.
[cheering]
[stammers] Hello. Hello. hello.
- Um...
- [mic feedback]
Thank you very much for being here.
My-My old restaurant
was named after my wife.
and then I thought. how could I
bring it back when she's not here with us?
But I guess I was looking at it wrong
because then I thought it could be
a tribute to her and to our son.
[camera shutters clicking]
That's why it's called Melissa & Adam
and. uh. that's the reason why.
- [applauding]
- [Max] Thank you. Thank you.
Hey. Anna.
Oh. okay.
[tense music playing]
[stammers] Great you're... that you're here.
But. uh.
any issues between us can wait. okay?
Not here. not now.
[Anna] No. it'll be quick.
Your sister. she cut me pretty good.
so I gotta get to the hospital.
My daughter is
in a juvenile detention center...
Yeah. yeah. for shooting me. Correct.
...with his daughter.
Yeah. he has a kid.
And they're in there together. which. um...
And. um. my daughter risked her life
to get me this.
[crowd murmurs. gasps]
[chuckles]
Okay.
All right. so you're bringing us a show...
[Anna] No. just
a little conversation our daughters had.
Okay. Anna...
[Natalie] Did Max make you do all of it?
[Nevaeh] Yeah. He told me
to break into your house.
spike the tea with acid.
seduce your brother...
make him bite off his own toe.
[chuckles. breathes shakily]
What does he want you to do now?
He wants me to kill you.
And he's not gonna stop
until he destroys your entire family.
[crowd exclaiming. murmuring]
Okay. thank you very much
for bringing that.
Um... [stammers]
...what kind of person are you. Anna?
You come here to. what.
to humiliate me with that shit?
With those fake voices? Come on.
Oh. you think that's all I have?
That's not all I have.
Ah.
What kind of person are you. Max?
[Amy] Max. I'm not sure.
I don't know if I can actually do it.
[Max] Yes. you can. Yes. you can.
It's right there.
Write the note
and-and-and pull the trigger.
[crowd gasps. chatters]
- [Amy] No. Max.
- Put that off.
Yes. Amy. set us both free.
This is who he is.
- This is who he is.
- Yes. Together.
Come on. just admit it. Max.
[Max] I know you want to. Amy. it's okay.
Amy Brancato confessed.
but you killed your wife.
You know that's not true. Okay?
You know that's not true.
Listen to your heart.
[Amy] Max. Melissa was...
No. no. no she was not.
[chuckles] Remember we fucked in her bed?
- [crowd gasps. murmuring]
- Turn that off. Turn that off!
- She was nothing to me.
- [exclaims]
[menacing music playing]
You shit all over Melissa
to convince your mistress
to blow her brains out.
Well. you must have
really wanted Melissa dead.
And you had to kill her
before the baby was born.
God forbid you have to pretend to be
a good husband and a good dad.
- [gasps. chokes]
- [gasping]
- Anna!
- [choking]
[grunts]
Fuck you.
- [person screams]
- [Max groans]
[crowd clamoring]
[officer] Don't move. you got it?
[mysterious music playing]
- [grunting]
- [camera shutter clicks]
[officer] Stay down.
[panting]
- [grunting]
- [officer] Okay. all right. get up.
[officer] Hey. hey!
Come on. Let's get you to a hospital.
[music ends]
[thunder rumbling]
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Yo. Nat. are you at home?
I'm at Paul's house. Why?
Oh. we just drove by your place
on our way out of town
and we just saw Zack
kinda just standing there.
Isn't he supposed to be.
like. in the hospital or something?
Also. if you wanna come wait out the storm
at our country house.
we have plenty of room.
Like. I would love you... [stammers]
- ...I'd love for you to be there.
- I have to go.
[call ends]
[wind gusting]
[Lexi] Tom.
I got Judge Levine
to reconsider your bail.
Convinced him
you're a trophy for the prosecutor.
You wrote my bail motion?
[Lexi] You're still an asshole.
but not a murderer.
Thanks. Lex.
I'm guessing you haven't seen
what your wife did yet.
What?
You should watch the video.
She's got guts.
[engine starts]
Zack!
[tense music playing]
Nat.
- [sighs]
- Sorry.
- Jesus. Zack.
- Hi.
- Glad to see you again.
- I'm so happy to see you.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Are you hurt?
- No.
- No?
How did you get here?
I walked. I don't have keys.
Where the hell is everyone?
I'll tell you inside. okay?
A lot has happened.
- Okay.
- I'll tell you everything.
[person speaking on PA system]
[Tom] Hey.
Hey.
[Tom] Um. Max is still
in custody. and. uh... I. uh...
I-I spoke to Nat on the phone.
She and Zack are. uh. at home.
Both are okay.
[chuckles]
How are you? How's your hand?
I'll heal.
Or I'll get a hook.
[both chuckle]
I'm so sorry.
[sighs]
I saw the video.
It was really brave.
We got him.
Yeah.
So what do we do now?
[Tom sighs]
Well. let's just get you home.
And then?
- I know I fucked up. Tom. I...
- [Tom] No. [stammers]
I'm not putting this all on you.
I. uh...
[Anna] I'm glad that you know the truth.
I love you.
[speaker beeps]
[announcer] Due to Hurricane Wesley.
Savannah is now under
immediate evacuation order.
Those who can leave should.
Oh. Lord.
Yeah. let's just
get me out of here. right?
[thunder rumbling]
[radio chatter]
[officer] Every jail in the county
just went into lockdown.
so settle in. We got a long ride.
Sir. Officer. please.
[officer] What's the problem?
I-I get seizures and I-I need my medicine.
It's in my pocket right here. please. sir.
Please. I can't take it out.
- [car door opens]
- Thank you. sir.
[car door closes]
[Anna] Natalie.
Zack.
- [Natalie breathing shakily]
- Hi. Mom.
- [Natalie] Hey.
- Hi.
[Anna] You're home. You're safe.
[breathes shakily]
Mom. what happened to your hand?
Hey.
I was lucky that I didn't lose a finger.
honey. [chuckles]
Why did you run away. huh?
- I wanted to come home.
- [sniffles]
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I'm okay. I...
- Okay.
[Zack] Sorry. just give me a moment.
- [Natalie breathes shakily]
- [Anna sighs]
[sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
Hey. mind if I...
Zack. when I was locked up
and had no idea where you were
or what happened to you...
It is Zack. right?
Yeah.
It's me.
You don't need to be scared. Or anything...
[Tom sighs]
You know. um.
when my brother was struggling...
he buried it all
and none of us knew how bad it was.
He didn't die in an accident.
It was just something
my parents told people.
And I was 14. so I copied 'em. right?
Why are you telling me now?
[Tom] Well. I guess for a long time.
I didn't wanna see
how bad things were with you.
It was easier for me
to just tell myself you'd get better.
[Tom sighs]
But sometimes things just
suck.
And we can't pretend otherwise.
We'll just get through it together.
I don't know what you want me to say.
[knocks on door]
Who did I kill this time?
Yeah. about that whole thing.
Where's Max?
[Grayson] Can we come in?
Yeah.
Max assaulted a cop.
Escaped from custody
a couple of hours ago.
[Grayson] I don't guess he'd be
dumb enough to come right back.
but given the issues between y'all
and the injuries
that he inflicted on our fellow officer.
better safe than sorry.
How long have y'all been home?
Uh. not long.
[electricity crackles]
[Grayson]
Hurricane Wes ain't fucking around.
You mind if we make sure
nobody's playing hide-and-seek?
- [Tom] No.
- [detective] Here.
You. upstairs. You. that way.
Listen. um.
I don't know if Cady killed his wife.
but I guess it's pretty clear
he set out to make y'all's life hell.
So. sorry we fucked up.
Let's make sure y'all are safe
and get the heck out of here.
[Anna] Nat. Zack. pack a bag.
We're getting out of here.
[thunder rumbles]
[tense music playing]
[phone chimes]
Hey. can I talk to you upstairs
for a second?
[police radio chatter]
Just game this out with me.
We move to a different state.
change our names.
- just wait for him to find us.
- [keypad beeping]
[Anna] What are you saying?
[Tom] You take the kids out of town.
I'll wait for him.
You're just going to kill him?
Eliminate the threat. For good.
- [door shuts]
- [keypad beeps]
What if he kills you?
- Have you considered that possibility?
- He is already killing us.
Death by a thousand cuts.
No. we have real evidence now.
Max Cady's going to prison.
[Tom] When?
He won't stop.
This fear that we're living with.
this will be our life and our kids' lives.
[Grayson] Y'all in here?
[sighs] Oh. you got your shotgun.
Can't say I blame you.
Well. you have a very angry possum
living under your porch.
but no Max Cady.
[wind whistling]
Listen. keep your alarm on
and leave town as soon as you can.
The storm's only getting worse.
We're just gonna throw some stuff
in a bag and be gone in 15 minutes.
All right. good.
[menacing music playing]
[thunderclap]
[wind howling outside]
[thuds]
[footsteps]
[footsteps continue]
[thudding]
[wind whistling]
[wind roaring]
Guys?
You all packed?
Nat?
- [wind whistling]
- [rain falling]
Nat?
- Tom!
- [laughs]
- [Tom grunts]
[grunts] Let him go! Let go of him!
- [Max] Gun down.
- [Tom] Let go!
Gun down!
If you hurt him. he will shoot.
- [screaming]
- Go on. Do it.
Hey. hey. hey. hey. hey. hey!
Okay. okay. okay!
Gun down!
Now!
Back. Back!
[exclaims]
- Hey. hey. hey. hey! Come on! Stop!
- [whimpers]
- [Max] All right.
- [Tom] Okay...
- [Anna exclaims]
- [Max] Oh. okay.
On the count of four. let's proceed.
- Over there. Over there.
- Okay.
All right.
Ms. Deveraux and Mr. Prosecutor.
please be seated.
Sit the fuck down. There.
Those two.
Right.
Now. here. Their wrists to the chair.
- Boy. stay there.
- It's okay.
[Max] Nice and tight.
Come on. Come on.
To the chairs. Come on.
All right. stand up. Stand up.
Now. you. her wrists.
Please don't do this. Dad.
Dad? You said "Dad"?
Okay. say. "Papá. Papá."
Just take me with you.
I-I'll go anywhere you want.
- You said you wanted to help me. right?
- Natalie.
Yeah. I said something like that. yeah.
but then you shot me.
Okay. turn the fuck around now.
You're gonna sit here.
All right.
Now.
we better make sure
he's not a danger to himself.
- No.
No. no. no. no. Max.
- You don't have to do that. No!
- [Anna] No. No. Zack!
- [Max] All right. Come here.
- [Anna] Zack. I'm right here.
- [Max] There.
- Oh. fuck.
- You've probably built a tolerance...
- [Anna] Max!
- [Tom] No! Don't do that. Max! No!
- ...but don't worry because this.
- this is a big one.
- No. no!
[Max] Just a little pinch.
[Tom] No!
- [Max] Wow. he goes fast.
- [Anna] Just look at me.
I'm right here. Okay? I'm right here.
- [Max] Look at that.
- [Anna] I'm right here.
[Max] Come here.
[Max. muffled] Okay. like that.
[normal] All right. now we have
the whole family together. Finally.
But. before we get started.
Tom. thank you so very much
for raising my kids. [laughing]
[Anna] Is that what you want to hear?
Y-You want me to say
that she's your daughter.
she's your daughter. She...
He-He's your son. You made him your son.
Okay? Okay. you win. Just let them leave.
- I can't let them leave.
- [Anna] No. you should let them leave.
I can't let them leave because...
Hey. stop it.
If I let them leave. I don't have my jury.
- All rise.
- [whimpers]
The People
versus Anna Deveraux and Tom Bowden
is now in session.
So. lady and little gentleman of the jury.
the evidence will show
that Ms. Deveraux and Mr. Bowden conspired
to send Max Cady to prison
for their own personal reasons.
Sit down. Hey. you got a Bible?
What?
Move to strike. Your Honor.
- [grunts. groans]
- Bible.
[stammers] They're usually black
with a cross on it.
What the fuck are you doing?
[Max] What the fuck am I doing?
Take a look at this.
Hey.
I want you to bite off your tongue for me.
Zack. don't listen!
Ah.
- No. no. no. Zack. Zack. Zack.
- Zack. don't do it. No!
- Bite down really slow. [hums]
- [Tom] Zack! Zack!
- [Anna] Zack! [gasps]
- [Tom] No.
- [Max] A little bit stronger. Keep going.
- [Anna] Okay. okay. okay. I swear.
I-I-I swear to tell the truth.
We swear to tell the whole truth. Max.
[Anna] I swear to tell the whole truth.
Okay. okay. okay. Boy. boy. boy.
Okay. wait for a second. Good job.
Ms. Deveraux.
Tell the jury the truth about
the deal you told Maximiliano Cady
that he should take.
- I... I got you a deal...
- [Max] Mm-hmm.
...to take the death penalty off the table.
Let me remind the witness
she's under oath.
That is exactly what happened. Max.
Permission to treat the other witness
as hostile. Your Honor.
- [groans]
- [Anna] Tom.
Okay. okay. okay. we conspired.
Is that what you want to hear?
We made it up.
What I want to hear is the truth. Anna.
For once in your fucking life. one truth.
Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
There was a leak.
[Tom groans]
From the jury room.
And the jury was deadlocked.
and they might even let you walk.
but I was scared of you. Max.
And I could have used that
to get you a good deal. but I didn't.
I did the opposite. and we put you away
for a very long time.
[thunderclap]
I could have been acquitted?
I could have been acquitted.
Do you hear that. jury?
She betrayed her own client. Yeah? Okay.
But that's not all. is it? That's not all.
Tell the jury what you fucking did.
Yes. I betrayed you.
No. no. Why did you want me gone?
'Cause I thought you killed your wife.
- No. No. No. no. no! Okay.
- [Tom] No. No! No!
In this court. perjury is not
- a slap on the wrist. okay?
- [Anna] Okay...
- [Max] There's severe penalties...
- [Anna] ...okay. okay.
[Max] ...for lying under oath.
You got that?
Okay. okay. okay.
I was scared that Nat was your daughter.
Ah! What was that? What'd you say?
- and I didn't want her to know you.
- [Max] Daughter.
I didn't want her to know
that her father was a monster.
"Monster." move to strike as prejudicial.
[Anna] Well. if you weren't
a monster then. you are one now.
[Max] Listen... [laughs]
Whoever I am today. you made me.
Do you understand that?
You both did it. You both did it together.
You condemned a man who was innocent!
- [Tom] We both...
- And you knew it!
- We both thought you were guilty!
- Fuckers!
Fuckers! Liars!
- We're telling the truth.
- [Max] Why would I believe your lies now?
- We're telling the truth!
- You wanna know? There is no truth
in your fucking life!
You are the lie!
Always lying!
Yesterday. she tried to make me believe
that I had a kid with my sister.
- [Anna cries]
- What the fuck is that?
Yes. that boy Luke is your son. Max.
[laughing]
[Anna] That boy Luke is your son. Max.
Was.
He's in the river now
with my fucked up sister
and that piece of shit thing
that I called a father.
And you know what?
He couldn't be my kid
because Crystal couldn't have kids. okay?
She was in a car accident. fucked her up.
All right. Lady and gentleman of the jury.
the prosecution is finished
with this witness for now.
Shangó. Shangó! Sí. gracias. Gracias!
I have carried you in my skin
so that this day would come.
[in Latin] Justice.
Fire.
Thunder and lightning.
[in English]
Today's the day and you are the judge!
Well. the courtroom is leaking.
but who cares?
Justice cannot wait.
I now call Tom Bowden to the stand.
Yeah. hey. speaking of leaks.
you knew about the jury. right?
It's not my job to be
your fucking second defense lawyer.
[Max] Okay. what was your job then?
To seek justice. maybe.
But what do you seek instead?
To keep a perfect conviction rate
for your own records.
You fucker.
And then not only with that.
but you fucked my lawyer.
And you both built
a life of privilege off of me.
off my pain. off my suffering.
off my time in prison.
That's what you guys did.
[Tom] I'll say
whatever words you want to hear.
But we did not sleep together
during your trial.
I was falling in love with her.
But nothing happened.
[thunderclap]
Ah. shit.
[groans] Fuck. Fuck. Oh.
Max. you hit your head pretty hard today.
If you have a brain injury.
you need to get to the hospital
or you could die.
I'm gonna be with you today.
Finally today with you.
[sighs] Can't wait.
[sighs]
Okay. uh.
I can go now with the closing arguments.
but I... I'm sure you've got an idea
what it's going to be like.
But. uh... Hey.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
[breathes shakily]
Yeah. like my dad said. go fuck yourself.
Okay. not guilty. Well. yeah. what?
Yeah. Your Honor. you're right.
she's not an impartial juror.
so disqualified.
You. Hey. boy.
Oh. fuck. You're still out there. right?
No. okay. so it looks like
it's going to be a directed verdict.
So let's listen.
Let's listen what he has to say.
[wind howling]
Shangó...
God of justice.
Orisha of thunder.
What do you rule?
[thunder rumbles]
- Guilty.
- [thunder rumbles]
With capital sentences
to be carried out immediately. Fine.
- No. no. no. no! No! No!
- [gasps. exclaims]
Max. that boy Luke
is your son with Melissa.
Think about it. Think about it.
My son with Melissa?
I can prove it.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Let me submit evidence. It's on my phone.
I'll get back to you later.
It's the only explanation.
Last text from Noa.
There's a certificate of home birth.
It says that Luke Cady
was born to Crystal Cady.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah. but Crystal can't have kids.
- can she? I know.
- No.
So where did the kid come from. Max?
- This your phone?
- Yeah.
Open it up.
Look at the date.
What?
That's right after Melissa went missing.
Yeah.
If Crystal can't have kids. Max.
where did she get the baby?
Do you see the scar on his side?
I think Crystal killed Melissa.
And she ripped him out of her.
Your sister stole your baby. Max.
No. no. no. no. no. no. no.
- Yes. Luke is your baby with Melissa.
- [Max] No. that cannot...
[Anna] That boy on the boat
was your son Adam.
and he was alive all the time
until you killed him.
- You killed him. Max.
- [Max] No. no. no. no.
[whimpers]
[Anna] You killed your own son.
[Max] No!
You killed him.
[sobbing]
[sighs]
[mouthing words] I got it.
- Run!
- [whimpering]
[panting]
[tense music playing]
You have jury duty.
[screams]
No! No! No!
- [grunts]
- [Max grunts. exclaims]
[screams]
[grunts]
[Max yells. grunts]
[whimpering]
Ah. [groaning]
[screaming]
[Max sighs]
[groaning]
[panting]
[grunts]
- Natalie. Natalie.
- [Tom] Grab the knife. Here. here...
Nat!
[Natalie screaming]
[screams] No!
[Tom grunts]
[Natalie] No! [screams]
[mysterious music playing]
[birds singing]
[mouthing words] Great job.
[menacing music plays]
No.
No!
[both grunting]
[grunts] Shit.
- No.
- [Max grunts]
[both grunting]
Zack. get a knife.
[Max exclaims]
[Tom groans]
[coughs]
[Max. Anna exclaim]
[groaning]
[Tom. Max grunt]
[gasps]
[grunting]
Tom!
Kill him!
Let him die in a cage.
[coughing]
[sobbing]
[hopeful music playing]
[music ends]
You all know what happened here.
in the house where Max Cady lived
while he planned his revenge
on the lawyers who put him away.
But what you don't know.
what you can never know.
is how it felt to be around Max Cady.
To bask in the warmth of his gaze.
But I can.
Because I loved Max.
[Anna] Natalie. it's time to eat.
["Everybody Knows This Is Nowhere"
playing]
I don't like to use hyperbole.
but if word gets out about
how good these cheeseburgers are...
Don't worry. It won't.
[both chuckle]
[Tom chuckles]
[music continues]
[exhales sharply]
[Natalie] Hey. Dad. need some help?
[Tom] Uh. sure.
Join the. uh. assembly line.
Just open one of those.
You good?
Mm-hmm. I'm good.
Who's the psychopath who ordered
no cheese. no lettuce. no bun?
- Guilty.
- Here. Well. in that case.
it looks fantastic.
[music ends]